<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<frequently-asked-questions>
    <question>
        <text>How do I join Beta.TrentonDucati.com?</text>
        <answer>In order to join the Beta.TrentonDucati.com site, select the 'Join Now' link at the top right of the page.
            A list of available subscription plans will be presented to you.
        </answer>
    </question>
    <question>
        <text>How will the charge for my Beta.TrentonDucati.com membership appear on my credit card statement?</text>
        <answer>All charges from Beta.TrentonDucati.com and associated websites will appear as "NS Entertain 18004199287".
        </answer>
    </question>
    <question>
        <text>How do I reset my password?</text>
        <answer>You can reset your forgotten password by clicking on the "Forgot Password" link that appears on the login page. This will generate a new password that is
            emailed to the address associated with your account. If you wish to choose a specific password, please contact Customer Service at:
            U.S. (toll free) 888.207.4534, International 980.505.8324, or email: support@adultpaysitesupport.com and we will be happy to help.
        </answer>
    </question>
    <question>
        <text>Why won't my movie play?</text>
        <answer>Many factors can affect the playback of video on the website: browser type, device type, type of connection you are using, etc. To receive personal assistance
            in resolving your issue, please contact our customer service via phone, chat or email during business hours.
        </answer>
    </question>
    <question>
        <text>Why is the site loading so slowly?</text>
        <answer>Site lag is usually caused by browser or connection issues. Please try clearing your browser's history, changing browsers, or refreshing your internet connec-
            tion. If this does not resolve your problems, please contact our customer service via phone, chat or email during business hours.
        </answer>
    </question>
    <question>
        <text>How often does Nakedsword.com add new content?</text>
        <answer>Content is updated daily, with 8 additions to the website each day. These additions can be in movies, scenes, or re-uploading previous removed content. Please
            be sure to check our 'Just Added' page for the newest content.
        </answer>
    </question>
    <question>
        <text>Can I watch 2 movies at one time?</text>
        <answer>We do not advise watching two movies at once, it will most likely cause buffering issues or cause the player to crash and stop streaming one or both of the
            films.
        </answer>
    </question>
    <question>
        <text>How do I add a scene or movie to my favorites?</text>
        <answer>To save a scene to your favorites for later viewing, select the plus sign with a circle around itthat appears at the lower right side of scenes. This will add the
            scenes to your favorite scene list.
        </answer>
    </question>
    <question>
        <text>Can I share my Beta.TrentonDucati.com membership with a friend?</text>
        <answer>We do not advise sharing any account information with anyone. You are limited to five active logins on an account from five different IP addresses. If you go
            over this five limit, you will be locked out of your account for 24 hours while the system resets your account limits.
        </answer>
    </question>
    <question>
        <text>Can I suggest a new studio that I'd like to see on nakedSword.com?</text>
        <answer>We always appreciate customer feedback, please be sure to contact our customer service department to let them know what you'd like to see added to the
            site.
        </answer>
    </question>
    <question>
        <text>How can I be a porn star?</text>
        <answer>You can do anything you set your mind to! If you are interested, please feel free to visit: model4nakedsword.com for all the information on how to apply.
        </answer>
    </question>
    <question>
        <text>Do you have an affiliate program?</text>
        <answer>If you are looking for an opportunity to make a little extra and want to promote our fantastic sites, please click here to join our affiliate program.
        </answer>
    </question>
    <question>
        <text>Why did my membership expire?</text>
        <answer>Most memberships end up expiring because we failed to receive your payment. This could be because there was an issue at the bank or maybe you forgot to
            update your credit card with us. Please feel free to contact our customer service department for assistance.
        </answer>
    </question>
    <question>
        <text>How can I change my membership type?</text>
        <answer>If you wish to change to a Monthly, Quarterly or Annual account - please contact our customer service department during regular business hours.
        </answer>
    </question>
    <question>
        <text>How do I cancel my membership?</text>
        <answer>You must contact customer service to cancel your account, either by email, Live Chat or by calling us during normal business hours.
        </answer>
    </question>
</frequently-asked-questions>