<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<terms-of-service>
    <terms>
        <term>
            <index>1.</index>
            <text>
                I, The Customer, affirm that I am at least 21 years of age.</text>
        </term>
        <term>
            <index>2.</index>
            <text>I, The Customer, hereby acknowledge tha explicit visual, audio and/or textual depictions of male
                homosexual conduct appear on this web site, that I am familiar with materials of this kind, that I am
                not offended by such materials and I am interested in viewing it. I am entering this website because it
                has adult content. I do not find content offensive or objectionable. I believe that as an adult I have
                the right to choose what I see and read, and I am choosing to enter this adult website to view adult
                content.
            </text>
        </term>
        <term>
            <index>3.</index>
            <text>I, The Customer, am fully aware of the laws and community standards of the locality and community to
                which I am transporting these materials and am solely responsible for my actions.
            </text>
        </term>
        <term>
            <index>4.</index>
            <text>I, The Customer, do not reside in a Nation, State, or Locality where this material is considered
                obscene: nor do I live in a Nation, State, County, or Locality where it is illegal to view, possess or
                distribute such sexually explicit material.
            </text>
        </term>
        <term>
            <index>5.</index>
            <text>I, The Customer, am requesting this site for my own non-commercial use in my own private residence.
            </text>
        </term>
        <term>
            <index>6.</index>
            <text>I, The Customer, acknowledge and accept that it is my responsibility to prevent from viewing any adult
                content on or from this website any person who is under the jurisdiction of any municipality, city,
                state, country, or other governmental entity where viewing adult content is prohibited by law. I, The
                Customer, understand that passive or active failure to uphold this responsibility will place me liable
                to civil and criminal prosecution.
            </text>
        </term>
        <term>
            <index>7.</index>
            <text>
                <section>
                    I, The Customer, acknowledge that the material found on this site is not suitable for minors or
                    persons who object to adult content of a homoerotic nature. I agree to take all due precautions to
                    prevent minors or persons who may find such content objectionable from accessing, viewing, or
                    downloading any material found on this site, such as but not limited to: implementing access
                    controls on my computer; implementing access controls on my web browser software; keeping my access
                    information out of the hands of minors; preventing others from using my user agreement credentials
                    to
                </section>
                <section>
                    ("cookie") to access sexually explicit material.
                </section>
            </text>
        </term>
        <term>
            <index>8.</index>
            <text>I, The Customer, agree that I must not permit any minor to see material found on this site. I agree to
                keep my computer, account and password safe from access by minors.
            </text>
        </term>
        <term>
            <index>9.</index>
            <text>I, The Customer, By entering this website, I agree to release, discharge, and hold harmless, The
                Merchant (the providers, owners and creators of this website) from any and all liability which might
                arise from the viewing, reading, and general consumption of adult content on this website on the part of
                myself or on the part of any other persons who may use mu hardware, software or security credentials
                with or without my permission to access this material.
            </text>
        </term>
        <term>
            <index>10.</index>
            <text>I, The Customer, agree that all information that I disclose to the Merchant, Beta.TrentonDucati.com, its
                agents, partners, and affiliates is solely my own, and is accurate, current, and does not infringe on
                the privacy of any others.
            </text>
        </term>
        <term>
            <index>11.</index>
            <text>I, The Customer, certify that I am the owner or beneficial holder of the credit card or other payment
                instrument used to make any purchases on Beta.TrentonDucati.com.
            </text>
        </term>
        <term>
            <index>12.</index>
            <text>I, The Customer, warrant that I will make any purchases from The Merchant, Beta.TrentonDucati.com, its agents,
                partners, and affiliates, in good faith and intend to pay for it.
            </text>
        </term>
        <term>
            <index>13.</index>
            <text>I, The Customer, agree that The Merchant, Beta.TrentonDucati.com, its agents, partners, and affiliates have
                the right to use any information that i disclose to them for any purposes they see fit.
            </text>
        </term>
        <term>
            <index>14.</index>
            <text>I, The Customer, agree that The Merchant, Beta.TrentonDucati.com, may capture details of my identity and
                Internet usage for the purposes of fraud and piracy reduction.
            </text>
        </term>
        <term>
            <index>15.</index>
            <text>I, The Customer, agree not to engage in fraudulent representation or behavior; I agree not to share,
                lend, give or otherwise allow usage by others of my user names or passwords, and otherwise to uphold
                fair practises for The Merchant, Beta.TrentonDucati.com.
            </text>
        </term>
        <term>
            <index>16.</index>
            <text>I, The Customer, agree that all materials and contents of this site are the sole property of The
                Merchant, Beta.TrentonDucati.com and its partners.
            </text>
        </term>
        <term>
            <index>17.</index>
            <text>I, The Customer, will not copy, upload, transmit, transfer, distribute, publish, modify or use for any
                commercial or other purpose any of the materials on this website, including the underlying HTML source
                code, without permission in writing and signed by the owner, The Merchant, Beta.TrentonDucati.com.
            </text>
        </term>
        <term>
            <index>18.</index>
            <text>I, The Customer, agree that I have no right to copy,save, capture, perform, redistribute, hack,
                pirate, burn, rip or otherwise attain personal possession of materials and content of The Merchant,
                Beta.TrentonDucati.com, except under the limited user agreement defined by The Merchant, Beta.TrentonDucati.com, and
                subject to revision at any time without disclosure to users by The Merchant, Beta.TrentonDucati.com. Any attempt
                to violate this may lead to immediate legal action.
            </text>
        </term>
        <term>
            <index>19.</index>
            <text>I, The Customer, agree to abide by all standards of behavior, disclosure and fair use determined by
                The Merchant, Beta.TrentonDucati.com for its users.
            </text>
        </term>
        <term>
            <index>20.</index>
            <text>I, The Customer, agree that The Merchant, Beta.TrentonDucati.com, has the sole right to determine standards of
                behavior, disclosure, and fair use for its users and may change those standards at any time. Notice will
                be sent via emails to all users, and they may cancel their membership if they do not agree with the
                changes.
            </text>
        </term>
        <term>
            <index>21.</index>
            <text>I, The Customer, agree indemnify and hold harmless the provider of this site from any and all civil
                claims or criminal charges that result from access, use, and viewing of the materials contained on this
                site.
            </text>
        </term>
        <term>
            <index>22.</index>
            <text>I, The Customer, acknowledge that all material found on this site is for ENTERTAINMENT ONLY.
            </text>
        </term>
        <term>
            <index>23.</index>
            <text>I, The Customer, agree that all visitors and members to this site support the principles of freedom of
                expression as articulated in the Constitution of the United States of America.
            </text>
        </term>
        <term>
            <index>24.</index>
            <text>I, The Customer, acknowledge that all images, content and files in this site are copyrighted material
                and re-use requires written consent of copyright owner.
            </text>
        </term>
        <term>
            <index>25.</index>
            <text>If I, The Customer, use these service in vilation of this Agreement, I understand I may be in
                violation of local, state, federal, international or other laws.
            </text>
        </term>
        <term>
            <index>26.</index>
            <text>I, The Customer, agree that any failure to comply with any of the above terms and conditions will
                result in the immediate terminations of my account, forfeiture of any credit owed me, and possible
                criminal or civil charges and prosecution. The Merchant, Beta.TrentonDucati.com, will undertake any legal action
                required to recover funds previously paid and compensation for damages incurred if any.
            </text>
        </term>
        <term>
            <index>27.</index>
            <text>Bookmarking or directly accessing any other page on this website and bypassing this Agreement shall
                constitute an implicit acceptance of this Agreement.
            </text>
        </term>
    </terms>
    <definitions>
        <definition>
            <index>1.</index>
            <title>Legal Definitions</title>
            <paragraphs>
                <paragraph>
                    <text>
                        "Member" or "Membership" as referred to in this document shall mean: The subscriber or user of a
                        valid
                        username and password for the site during the term of membership.
                    </text>
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <text>
                        "Site" as referred to in this document shall mean: The website for which you are purchasing a
                        username and password from NS Entertainment in order to access the site and its materials and
                        obtain
                        the benefits of membership.
                    </text>
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <text>
                        "Subscriber", as referred to in this document shall mean: The End-user / Consumer, of the
                        services
                        of the site and holder of a valid username and password for the site. "Access rights", as
                        referred
                        to in this document shall mean: The combination of unique username and password that is used to
                        access a site. An access rights is a license to use a site for a period of time that is
                        specified.
                    </text>
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <text>
                        "Bookmarking", as referred to in this document shall mean: The act of placing a URL into a
                        temporary
                        file on the subscriber's browser so that the subscriber mat return to that page at a future date
                        directly, without passing through any pages that may have proceeded.
                    </text>
                </paragraph>
            </paragraphs>
        </definition>
        <definition>
            <index>2.</index>
            <title>Description of Services</title>
            <paragraphs>
                <paragraph>
                    <text>
                        WMM Holdings LCC will provide one access right to access the site and its contents for which you
                        are
                        purchasing membership.
                    </text>
                </paragraph>
            </paragraphs>
        </definition>
        <definition>
            <index>3.</index>
            <title>Billing</title>
            <paragraphs>
                <paragraph>
                    <text>
                        NSEntertainment will appear on your credit card, bank statement, or phone bill for all charges
                        made. If multiple venues are joined utilizing any payment method, your statement will list each
                        individual purchase comprising the transaction. Merchant, Beta.TrentonDucati.com, may include other
                        information on your statement based on credit card association, telephone regulation, NACHA and
                        any
                        other mandated rules and regulations. If you elect to use your checking account to purchase a
                        subscription to this website, an ACH debit will be drawn on their account. Your agreement with
                        these
                        Terms * Conditions is your approval for Merchant, Beta.TrentonDucati.com, to issue an ACH debit to
                        your
                        account.
                    </text>
                </paragraph>
            </paragraphs>
        </definition>
        <definition>
            <index>4.</index>
            <title>Payment / Fee</title>
            <paragraphs>
                <paragraph>
                    <text>
                        Sites may have periodic subscriptions feds that are defined by the owners of the site at the
                        time of
                        the initial enrolment for subscription. The member is responsible for such fees according to the
                        terms of the site.Once a member has the ability to access the site using the access rights
                        assigned
                        to the member, subscription fees become non-refundable.
                    </text>
                </paragraph>
            </paragraphs>
        </definition>
        <definition>
            <index>5.</index>
            <title>Automatic Recurring Billing (If Selected By You On The Sign Up Page)</title>
            <paragraphs>
                <paragraph>
                    <text>
                        As determined by the content provider of the site, subscription fees may be automatically
                        renewed at
                        the end of the original term selected, for a similar period of time, unless notice is received
                        from
                        the subscriber seven (7) days before renewal. All special introductory offer Members shall be
                        exempt
                        from the 7 day notification requirement, but subscriber must notify NS Entertainment 24 hours
                        prior
                        to the end of the trial/special offer period in order to cancel automatic renewal. All
                        trial/special
                        offer memberships shall renew at the stated membership rate. The maximum term of this agreement
                        is
                        100 months. Unless and until tis agreement is cancelled in accordance with the terms hereof,
                        subscriber hereby authorizes NS Entertainment to charge subscriber's chosen payment method for
                        any
                        and all additional purchases of services and entertainment provided by the site.
                    </text>
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <text>
                        In the event of an unsuccessful recurring payment, and administration fee of up to $2.00 may be
                        applied in order to keep a subscription temporarily active until the full subscription fee can
                        be
                        processed successfully.
                    </text>
                </paragraph>
            </paragraphs>
        </definition>
        <definition>
            <index>6.</index>
            <title>Electronic Receipt</title>
            <paragraphs>
                <paragraph>
                    <text>
                        Subscribers will receive and email receipt to their email provided upon initial subscription.
                        Subscriber may, at any time, request a copy of the account of charges made for the life of their
                        membership to the site. Subscriber foregoes this right if such request is not made. Request must
                        ne
                        made directly to NS Entertainment. To contact NS Entertainment, refer to the Questions and
                        Contact
                        Information at the end of this document.
                    </text>
                </paragraph>
            </paragraphs>
        </definition>
        <definition>
            <index>7.</index>
            <title>Cancellation</title>
            <paragraphs>
                <paragraph>
                    <text>
                        At any time, and without cause, subscription to the service may be terminated by either NS
                        Entertainment, the site, or the subscriber upon notification of the other by electronic or
                        conventional mail, or by telephone or fax. When the member requests the termination,
                        subscription
                        fees are not refunded.Subscribers are liable for charges incurred by them until termination of
                        service.
                    </text>
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <text>
                        If you request cancellation or request a refund from NS Entertainment, your bank card issuer, or
                        phone company due to unauthorized or fraudulent use, NS Entertainment can at its discretion, to
                        prevent further unauthorized use, clock your information from use at all NS Entertainment
                        clients'
                        websites. This will not however prevent unauthorized use at non-NS Entertainment clients'
                        websites,
                        and is not a substitution for your contacting your appropriate channels to prevent further
                        misuse.
                    </text>
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <text>
                        If you are taking advantage of a "Free" trial period through a credit card, please be aware of
                        the
                        following: NS Entertainment will request and your bank will immediately put a "Reserved Funds"
                        hold
                        on your credit card for the amount of the subscription plan you have selected. If the free trial
                        is
                        cancelled within the timeframe allowed by the website, it typically takes the banking system 7
                        to 10
                        days to remove the credit card hold from these funds. Please understand that NS Entertainment
                        has no
                        way to remove this hold. During the trial period and for a minimum of 7 to 10 days after you
                        cancel,
                        these funds are considered out of your bank even though technically they are still there, and
                        you
                        could overdraw or exceed the limits of your account. You are responsible for any charges imposed
                        by
                        your credit card issuing bank for exceeding your account limits or overdrawing your account.
                    </text>
                </paragraph>
            </paragraphs>
        </definition>
        <definition>
            <index>8.</index>
            <title>Refunds</title>
            <paragraphs>
                <paragraph>
                    <text>
                        When the member request the termination, subscription fees are NOT refundable. Should a refund
                        be
                        issued by NS Entertainment, all refunds will be credited solely to the payment method used in
                        the
                        original transaction. NS Entertainment will not issue refunds by cash, check, or to another
                        credit
                        card or payment mechanism.
                    </text>
                </paragraph>
            </paragraphs>
        </definition>
        <definition>
            <index>9.</index>
            <title>Bookmarking</title>
            <paragraphs>
                <paragraph>
                    <text>
                        Subscriber agrees that at any time they will not bookmark any page to the site that will allow
                        the
                        subscriber to bypass the terms and conditions on the site upon entering. If such a bookmark
                        exists,
                        said bookmark will constitute full agreement to said terms and conditions as well as to
                        admission
                        that subscriber is of legal age of majority in their state, country or region.
                    </text>
                </paragraph>
            </paragraphs>
        </definition>
        <definition>
            <index>10.</index>
            <title>Authorization of use</title>
            <paragraphs>
                <paragraph>
                    <text>
                        Subscribers to the site are hereby authorized a single access rights to access the service or
                        material located at this website. This access rights shall be granted for sole use to 0ne
                        subscriber. All memberships are provided for personal use and shall not be used for any
                        commercial
                        purposes or by any commercial entities. Commercial use of either the site or any material found
                        within is strictly prohibited unless authorized by the website. No material within the site may
                        be
                        transferred to any other person or entity, whether commercial or non-commercial. In addition,
                        materials may not be modified, or altered. Materials may not be displayed publicly, or used for
                        any
                        rental, sale or display. Materials shall extend to copyright, trademarks, or other proprietary
                        notices there from. NS Entertainment and the site reserve the right to terminate this access
                        rights
                        at any time if the terms of this agreement are breached. In the case terms are breached, you
                        will be
                        required to immediately destroy any information or material printed, downloaded or otherwise
                        copied
                        from the site.
                    </text>
                </paragraph>
            </paragraphs>
        </definition>
        <definition>
            <index>11.</index>
            <title>Transfer of Access Rights</title>
            <paragraphs>
                <paragraph>
                    <text>
                        Access to the site is through a combination of username and a password. Subscribers may not
                        under
                        any circumstances release their access rights to any other person, and are required to keep
                        their
                        access rights strictly confidential. NS Entertainment will not release passwords for any reason,
                        to
                        anyone other than the subscriber, except as may be specifically required by law or court order.
                        Unauthorized access to the site is a breach of this Agreement and a violation of the law.
                        Subscribers acknowledge that the owner of the site may track through the use of special software
                        each subscriber's entry to the site. If any breach of security, theft or loss of access rights,
                        or
                        unauthorized disclosure of access rights information occurs, subscriber must immediately notify
                        NS
                        Entertainment or the site of said security breach. Subscriber will remain liable for
                        unauthorized
                        use of service until NS Entertainment or this site is notified of the security breach by e-mail
                        or
                        telephone.
                    </text>
                </paragraph>
            </paragraphs>
        </definition>
        <definition>
            <index>12.</index>
            <title>Sanction and Approval of Adult Material</title>
            <paragraphs>
                <paragraph>
                    <text>
                        The owner of this site may be providing material or images intended for an age restricted
                        audience.
                        Access to this site is intended solely for people who are of legal age in the jurisdiction where
                        this site is being viewed and are at least 18 years of age in the US (21 in AL, MS, NE, and WY),
                        who
                        wish to access visual images, audio sounds, and verbal descriptions of a sexually oriented and
                        frankly erotic nature. Materials available within this site may include depictions that are
                        visually
                        graphic in nature and portrayals of nudity or sexual acts and should not be accessed by anyone
                        who
                        finds such material offensive in nature, or by anyone who simply does not wish to e exposed to
                        such
                        materials. By purchasing a membership or access rights, you are implicitly making the following
                        statements: "I affirm and swear that as of this moment, under penalty of Perjury, I am of legal
                        age
                        in the jurisdiction where this site is being viewed and are at least 18 years of age in the US (
                        21
                        in AL, MS, NE, and WY). I will not permit any persons who are not of legal age in the
                        jurisdiction
                        where this site is being viewed and are at least 18 years of age in the US ( 21 in AL, MS, NE,
                        and
                        WY) to view or access in any way any materials found on this website. In understand that by
                        accessing this website, I will be exposed to materials that may include but are not limited to,
                        visual images, audio sounds, and verbal descriptions of a sexually oriented and frankly erotic
                        nature, portrayals of nudity, and sexual acts. I affirm that I am not offended by such
                        materials,
                        and that such materials are legal in my community. I am volunteering to view, hear, and access
                        such
                        materials on my own volition, and I choose to do so because I want to view/rea/hear or otherwise
                        access such materials for my own enjoyment, information or entertainment. My choice is a
                        manifestation of my interest in such matters, which is healthy and normal, and is also held by
                        most
                        adults in my area. I am completely familiar with the standards held in my community, and the
                        material I expect to access in this site falls within these standards. In my experience, the
                        average
                        adult in my community accepts the consumption of such materials by willing adults in
                        circumstances
                        such as this, which offer reasonable insulation from the materials for minors, and unwilling
                        adults. Adults in my community will accept the standards displayed within the site, and will not
                        find any of the material patently offensive"
                    </text>
                </paragraph>
            </paragraphs>
        </definition>
        <definition>
            <index>13.</index>
            <title>Supplementary Terms and Conditions</title>
            <paragraphs>
                <paragraph>
                    <text>
                        The site may have additional Terms and Conditions that are an integral part of their offering to
                        the
                        Subscriber, and are in addition of these Terms and Conditions. Such Terms and Conditions as
                        listed
                        at the site will in way invalidate any of the Terms and Conditions listed here. All Terms listed
                        apply to NS Entertainment, the site, and the subscriber. I understand that by having checked the
                        acknowledgment of NS Entertainment's Terms and Conditions, I am affirming that I have read and
                        understand the terms of this account and authorize the NS Entertainment to bill my chose payment
                        method in accordance with the current terms and conditions.
                    </text>
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <text>
                        This agreement is governed by the laws of the United States.
                    </text>
                </paragraph>
            </paragraphs>
        </definition>
        <definition>
            <index>14.</index>
            <title>Severability</title>
            <paragraphs>
                <paragraph>
                    <text>
                        If any provision of this Agreement shall be held to be invalid of unenforceable for any reason,
                        the
                        remaining provisions shall continue to be valid and enforceable. If a court finds that any of
                        this
                        Agreement is invalid or unenforceable, but that by limiting such provision it would become valid
                        or
                        enforceable, then such provision shall be deemed to be written, constructed, and enforced as so
                        limited.
                    </text>
                </paragraph>
            </paragraphs>
        </definition>
        <definition>
            <index>15.</index>
            <title>Notice</title>
            <paragraphs>
                <paragraph>
                    <text>
                        Notices by the site to subscribers may be given by means of electronic messages through the
                        site, by
                        a general posting on the site, or by conventional mail. Notices by subscribers may be given by
                        electronic messages, conventional mail, telephone or fax unless otherwise specified in the
                        Agreement. All questions, complaints, or notices regarding the site must be directed to NS
                        Entertainment. All cancellations of service to a site must also be directed to NS Entertainment.
                    </text>
                </paragraph>
            </paragraphs>
        </definition>
    </definitions>
    <contact-info>
        <paragraph>
            Questions and Contact Information All Questions to NS Entertainment regarding these terms and conditions
            must be directed to:
        </paragraph>
        <informations>
            <entry>NS Entertainment</entry>
            <entry>WMM Holdings, LLC</entry>
            <entry>2176 Shattuck Ave</entry>
            <entry>Berkeley</entry>
            <entry>California</entry>
            <entry>94704</entry>
            <entry>United States of America</entry>
            <entry>email us</entry>
            <entry>U.S. (TOLL FREE) 888.207.4534</entry>
        </informations>
    </contact-info>
    <footer>
        This records required by section 2257 of title 18, United States Code, with respect to this graphical material,
        are kept by the custodian of records at the individual studios represented in the site.
    </footer>
</terms-of-service>